Stealing Han's dishes,so we don't have to clean our at home is genius.
太有才了 把餐館的碟子偷回去 咱家就不用洗碗了
And a little sad.
也略可悲
You kidding? This is the greatest thing that's happened to me since I got my period this morning.
不是吧? 自打今早大姨媽駕到 這算是最振奮的事情了
Max,Caroline,you're stealing my dishes?
Max Caroline 你們偷店裡的碟子?
Damn it,I didn't think you could see up this high.
靠 沒想到這麼高你也看得見
And I didn't think you could sink this low.
我也沒想到 你們竟然這麼沒下限
Okay,stop,you're already robbing me blind with your "I'm a waitress" scam.
住手吧 你們打著服務生的旗號 已經快把我騙空了
Sorry,but things have gotten kind of messy at home.
對不起啦 但家裡事情有點亂
Yesterday,I had to take a shower to shower off the shower I took.
昨天 我不得不去沖澡 來洗掉澆了我一身的東西
You two should get a cleaning lady.
你們該請個清潔女工
I have a woman I pay to clean my apartment.
我就花錢請人清理我的公寓
She is expensive,but she may charge you less if you don't also have sex on her.
價錢不菲啊 但你們要是不和她搞 估計便宜點
I'll look into it.
我查查去
My grandmother cleaned the house free of charge.
我奶奶 給人打掃屋子都不收錢
Of course she didn't have a say in the matter.
當然了 收不收錢 由不得她說了算
Let's just ask Sophie. She has a cleaning service.
我們就問Sophie吧 她不是開家政服務的嘛
We have to do something.
總得採取點行動啊
Yesterday,I saw a roach walk out of our apartment.
昨天還看到一蟑螂 大搖大擺爬出我們家
Look.
你看
I'm gonna tell you what I told that guy who asked me to use my butt to smuggle opium.
上回有人要我用菊花夾帶鴉片 我就重複一下對他說的話好了
I'll do it!
我會做的!
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Sync: YTET-   定风波
-=伊甸園美劇 http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=伊甸園字幕站  http://ytet.org/=- 榮譽出品 本字幕僅供學習交流，嚴禁用於商業途徑
2.Broke.Girls Season 03 Episode 09
破產姐妹 第三季 第09集
Be ready,Max.
準備好 Max
We have to leave as soon as the cleaning lady gets here.
清潔工一來 我們就得走的
It's housekeeper etiquette.
家政服務的規矩
In my old life,I go to spin class and lunch with friends,but you and I will just go outside
換作以前 我就去上動感單車課 再跟朋友吃午飯 不過你和我
and watch the guy who just got out of jail do pull-ups on the light post.
就去外面 看剛出獄的傢伙 在燈柱上做引體向上好了
Calvin's out?
Calvin從裡面放出來了?
I'm not gonna leave.
我才不走呢
I want to watch her clean up my mess.
我得看著她收拾我的爛攤子
Yeah,baby.
爽一下
I've waited my whole life to have a servant.
這輩子 可就等著有人伺候我了
I thought you were gonna be it for the first few weeks and then I realized you can't do anything.
你剛來的那幾周 我還以為等到人了 結果發現 你啥也不會
And even though Sophie gave us a discount,the maid still has to call me "Your Highness."
雖然Sophie給我們打折 這姑娘 還是得叫我"女王陛下"(highness)
Mostly because I'm pretty "highness" right now.
主要是因為 我現在嗨(highness)得很
Hi,girls.
姑娘們
Here I am.
我來了
Sophie from Sophie's Choice Cleaning Service.
"蘇菲的選擇"家政服務的Sophie
Meet your cleaning lady Paulina.
這位是你們的清潔女工Paulina
Paulina,meet the girls.
Paulina 見過姑娘們
She'd shake hands,but she only has one arm.
她也想握手 但她只有一條胳膊
Sophie,she can hear you.
Sophie 她聽的見誒
So what? I know I'm missing arm.
那又怎樣? 我知道自己少條胳膊
It's not news.
有什麼新鮮的
So she lost an arm.
她丟了條胳膊
I lost my gold earring down the garbage disposal
我還把一隻金耳環 掉在垃圾通道裡了
but I was too afraid to reach into it because,well,yeah.
但不敢伸手進去撈 因為... 是吧
Don't worry.
不要擔心
I have one arm but I clean like I have three.
我雖然只有一條胳膊 但幹起活來 像有三頭六臂
I put on more makeup,then I start.
我再去化點妝 就開始幹活
I'm sorry. I didn't realize when I ordered a cleaning lady I had to specify I wanted one with two arms.
抱歉 我不知道打電話預約清潔工時 還得指明 要兩條胳膊的
You can't afford two arms.
兩條胳膊的你們請不起
You said you wanted a good price.
不是說要價錢合適的嗎
Half the arms,half the price.
少一半胳膊 少一半價錢
Is that how she lost the arm,Sophie?
難道她的胳膊就是這樣沒有的 Sophie?
You cut it off so we could get a discount?
為了替我們省錢 把她胳膊鋸了?
Oh,yeah,sure. Yeah,I sawed off her arm so I could save you 10 bucks.
是呢 我把她胳膊鋸了 好給你們省十塊錢
I start in bedroom.
從臥室開始了
Wait,before you do,one question.
等等 開工前 問個事兒
How'd you lose it? James Franco situation?
胳膊怎麼沒有的? James Franco那樣嗎? ("127小時")
You had to cut it off to get loose?
一定要鋸掉 不然沒法脫身嗎?
You're not saying no.
你竟然沒有否定哇
Oh,you know what,let's not go there.
我說 別扯那些了
You know,it happened,it was in the past.
過去的事 就過去了啦
I was trapped under this big truck.
我被卡在一輛大卡車底下
We get it.
知道了啦
I drove over your arm.
我開車把你胳膊碾了
Hey,don't even bother looking for my good jewelry in there because I'm already wearing all of it.
不用費神找我的值錢首飾 我全戴著呢
Oh,I'm jealous I don't have arm to wear cheap jewelry.
都沒有胳膊戴便宜貨 我好嫉妒啊
Max,I feel bad for her. See? This is why you leave.
Max 我為她感到難過 早說叫你出門啦
In case they show up with too much makeup and not enough arms.
帶著滿臉大濃妝 還缺胳膊的阿姨來 可怎麼好
Relax,she's tough. Reminds me of a young me.
行了 她很飆的 不禁想起年輕時的我
Which means I better go hide my pills from her.
也就是說 我得趕緊把藥藏起來 免得她找到
Max,she scares me.
Max 快被她嚇死了
Oh,come on,she's armless.
得了吧 她都沒胳膊的(無害的)
Everything okay? You need any help?
順利嗎? 要不要幫忙?
I didn't get this far in this business by taking help.
我幹這行這麼多年 可不是靠人幫忙
Help me! Can't you see I got one arm?
幫我一把啊! 沒見我只有一隻手嗎?
Not gonna be a problem.
沒問題哈
I would occasionally help my maid...
我以前也會偶爾幫幫女工的忙
- You're not interested. - Lift!
- 你完全沒興趣 - 抬起來!
Lift,weak girl. Lift.
小弱雞啊 用力抬!
Max,come here. We need help lifting your mattress.
Max 快來 一起把你床墊抬起來
Can you give us a hand?
搭把手吧?
No! Leave it alone! Leave it alone! Don't lift up the mattress!
不要! 放下! 不要抬床墊!
Porno.
黃書
Your mind is as dirty as your apartment!
你的思想跟你的公寓一樣髒!
Yes,it's porn. So what? What's the big deal?
黃書又怎樣啊? 有什麼大不了?
It's just the body in its natural form,spread-eagle on a motorcycle.
就是最原始自然的人體 呈"X"狀 架在摩托車上
Why is so much of it from the '80s?
怎麼好多都是80年代的?
I like mustaches,okay?
我喜歡有鬍子的好嗎
And it's multitasking. I'm looking for my father.
再說我還身兼任務 看看能不能找到我爸
Stop looking. Stop looking right now.
別看了 別看了
Why are you suddenly embarrassed? Porn hub is your homepage.
怎麼突然不好意思了? pornhub不是你瀏覽器主頁嗎?
Hey,is this a brochure for pastry school?
這是糕點學校的傳單嗎?
Why are you hiding a pastry school brochure?
糕點學校的傳單 幹嗎藏起來?
Your face is a pastry school brochure!
你才是糕點學校傳單呢!
Max,it's great you're interested in pastry school.
Max 你對糕點學校有興趣 是好事啊
- I don't know why you're embarrassed. - Your face is embarrassed!
- 你尷尬什麼呀 - 你才尷尬呢!
Come on,I really think that this is something we should talk about.
別這樣 我覺得我們可以談談這事
Your face is something we should talk about!
你才是我們應該談的!
You made the scary one mad.
你把那個嚇人的妞氣壞了
That was dumb move.
蠢啊
Your face was a dumb move!
你才蠢!
Max?
Max?
Max,you never came home after you stormed out,so I brought you your uniform.
衝出家門就沒見你回來 只好把你工作服帶來了
Max?
Max?
I live here now.
我現在住這兒了
My new roommates,the broom and the mop,don't sneak around looking at my stuff.
我的二位新室友 掃帚和拖把 不會偷偷翻別人東西
I got everything I need.
我啥也不缺
Whiskey,toothbrush,toothpaste.
威士忌 牙刷 牙膏
Well,maybe your new broommatewill hold back your hair when you drink too much.
也許你的掃帚新室友 也會在你喝到吐時 幫你擼著頭髮
Which,from the looks of it,will be in about an hour.
看這樣子 也就一小時後的事兒吧
Max,we really need to talk about this brochure.
Max 這傳單 我們真得聊聊
Look,just because I have a pastry school brochure doesn't mean I'm actually gonna go to pastry school.
我有糕點學校的傳單 又不代表 我要去上糕點學校
Just like having those porn magazines doesn't mean I'm actually gonna ride around on a tiger
一樣的道理 我有色情雜誌 又不代表我要騎老虎身上
performing unspeakable acts with sailors,probably.
和水手們一起表演 無法言說的情節
Pastry school is the same as porn.
糕點學校和色情就是一回事
It's just a dumb fantasy.
就是愚蠢的幻想
Pastry school is not like porn.
糕點學校和色情 怎麼能是一回事
There is nothing in this brochure about a girl-on-girl croissant.
這傳單上可沒有半點 "女女可頌麵包"的內容
That's good toothpaste.
這牙膏太優質了
Please stop brushing your teeth. We have a shift to do later.
別刷牙了好嗎? 一會兒要上班的
Okay,the Manhattan school of pastry...
好了 曼哈頓糕點學校
Your face is the Manhattan school of pastry.
你才曼哈頓糕點學校呢
You know it isn't.
你明知道不是
Max,you could go here for real.
Max 你想去就可以去的
Tuition is only $3,000 a year. A lot,but doable.
學費一年三千 多是多 但可以辦到的嘛
"A lot but doable?"
"多是多 但可以辦到?" ("大是大 但是可以搞")
Are we talking about pastry school or fat guy at last call?
是說糕點學校 還是酒吧快關門了 還守在店裡的胖子?
Here we are,Max. Your dream starts now.
到了 Max 你的夢想就要開始了
What,the one where I'm a black mermaid?
我是黑美人魚的那個夢想嗎?
Would you relax? We're just gonna look around and get an application.
別那麼沖 我們就四處看看 再拿個申請表
See all that gorgeous equipment you get to use if you went here?
看到了嗎? 要是來上學 就能用那些漂亮裝備了
Finally you'd have a mixing bowl that's not a hollowed-out watermelon.
終於不用拿挖空的西瓜 代替攪拌碗了
Can you help me? She's holding me against my will.
能幫幫我嗎? 她綁架我
She's kidding.
她開玩笑的
If you keep this up,young lady,you are not getting ice cream after.
這位姑娘 你要是再鬧 一會兒不去吃冰淇淋了
Fine!
好啦!
- Come on,here's the office. - Whatever. Are we almost done here?
- 來吧 辦公室在這裡 - 隨便 完事了嗎?
I got a court date later.
我一會兒還有法庭約會呢
I'm not sure we're in the right place.
不知道是不是來對了地方
Are any of us,really?
又有誰知道呢?
We'd like an application. Could you help us?
我們想填個申請表 能幫忙嗎?
Oh,God,I hope so.
天哪 我也想幫忙
I wasn't expecting something this high-pressure my first day back.
第一天回來上班 沒料到有那麼緊張的事情
Let's just say I've been under observation at the nuthouse.
這麼說吧 精神病院一直在觀察我
Okay,application.
好好 申請表
It's for Max,here. She was very impressed by your brochure.
是Max想申請 你們的傳單做得很好呀
Oh,pastry school. Exciting,right?
糕點學校 好興奮哈?
I was a chef here once. And then I wasn't.
我也曾是這裡的廚師 然後就不是了
Oh,look. Found the application.
啊 找到申請表了
Really didn't think I was gonna be able to handle that.
真沒想到我還能處理好這件事
Bebe,if you...
Bebe 要是你...
Bonjour. Good morning.
好啊 早上好
Chef Nicolas,these girls are here for an application.
Nicolas主廚 這兩位姑娘是來申請的
Don't worry,I handled it. Almost didn't,then I did.
別擔心 我處理好了 差點掉鏈子 不過處理得挺好
Nice work,Bebe.
做的好 Bebe
Oh,do I detect a French accent? Oui?
法國口音? 我沒聽錯吧? 是不?
Oh,my God,I can't watch.
媽呀 眼瞎了
French,indeed. I'm chef Nicolas Saintcroix,owner and head chef. Bienvenue.
我是法國人 Nicolas Saintcroix 這裡的老闆和主廚 歡迎
Caroline Channing.
Caroline Channing
Is it over yet?
酸完了嗎?
This is Max. The application's for her.
這是Max 是她要申請
'Sup,Frenchie? You eat snails?
法國佬 蝸牛吃不吃?
It looks like Bebe forgot the second page.
Bebe好像忘了給你第二頁
Oh,boy,forgot the second page. That's not good.
媽呀 忘了第二頁 要壞事
I thought I handled it. Didn't handle it.
我以為搞定了呢 原來沒有
It's okay,Bebe. Breathe in.
沒事的 Bebe 吸氣
Breathe out.
呼氣
That's good stuff.
太有用了
She was quite brilliant.
她以前很聰明的
Then she wasn't.
然後就不是了
Here. Fill that out. And the next step is the pastry exam.
給 把表填好 下一步是做糕點測試
Applicants will have to make a classic tart,bring them in tomorrow for me to taste,
申請者要做一個經典果餡餅 明天帶來 讓我嘗嘗
and we will go from there. Sound good?
然後再決定 可以嗎?
Whatever. Maybe I'll think about it.
隨便 沒準我會考慮考慮
Okay,well,maybe you will. Nice meeting you both.
好 沒準你會的 幸會啊
Hope to see you tomorrow,chef.
希望明天見咯 廚師
He called me chef!
他叫我廚師誒
- Yay! Let's go get ice cream! - No!
- 耶! 我們去吃冰淇淋吧! - 不行
You should get started on that tart. It's due tomorrow.
你得回去做果餡餅了 明天要交的
I got plenty of time. Besides,pressure ups my game.
時間多著呢 再說 壓力越大做得越好
I perform my best when there's a gun to my head.
拿槍對著我腦袋 我能做出尖貨來
Ask any of my ex-boyfriends.
隨便找個前男友問問就知道
This is so not how I prepare for tests.
我可完全不是這樣準備測試的
I studied three weeks for a pap smear.
做個宮頸塗片 我都要研究三周
Don't worry,I got this.
別擔心 我有數的
A tart's just like a cookie with some pudding on it,right?
果餡餅 就是餅乾上面堆點布丁吧?
Max,what is going on in here?
Max 怎麼回事?
Turns out a tart's more than a cookie with some pudding on it!
果餡餅 可不只是餅乾上堆布丁!
You've been in here six hours. You said you had this.
你在這兒都六小時了 你說能搞定的
I thought I had this! Turns out I don't! I haven't even finished a shell.
我以為能啊! 結果不行! 連皮子都沒做出來!
I didn't know there was a shell. Did you know there was a shell?
都不知道要做皮子的! 你知道要做皮子嗎?
Everybody knows there's a shell!
是人都知道果餡餅有皮子的好嗎!
What the shell is wrong with you?
媽蛋的 你怎麼回事啊?
I'm a tart who can't make a tart!
我是個連果餡餅(tart) 也不會做的騷貨(tart)!
You could've made nine shells by now.
九張皮子都做出來了好嗎
I did. They're all in here. Look.
我做了! 都在這裡 你看!
It's like Shell-mageddon!
簡直是皮子的末日戰場!
Oh,screw it. This one's gonna be there in a minute.
不管了 這盆反正也會倒進去的
Let's just get it over with.
還不如這就倒了
No,you can do this. Here. Here. This still looks ready to go.
別啊 你能行的 這盆看起來還挺好
Look at me. Look at me. I'm a waste of two arms.
你看我啊! 長兩條胳膊簡直是浪費
I can't make a tart!
連果餡餅都做不來
How's the tart coming?
果餡餅做得怎樣了?
Han,you're not safe. Leave.
Han 這裡不安全 快出去
You haven't even finished the shell? That's the easiest part!
皮子都沒做好? 那是最簡單的步驟了
Han,this is your face.
Han 這就是你的臉
Well,I should get going.
好了好了 我出去
I didn't know she could take bitch to the next level.
哪知道她的碧池作風 還能更上一層樓
I am so screwed!
我算是完蛋了
I finally found a situation my boobs can't get me out of!
終於迎來了一個 靠胸也不能解決的問題!
Hey,Max. Now,I have all the faith in the world in you.
Max 我可是最最相信你了
But here's a tart from Stop 'n Shop in case you wanted to hand this one in.
不過這個便利店的果餡餅 你想把它交上去也行
No,Earl. Max is not a cheater.
不行 Earl Max不會作弊的
Since when?
幾時不會了?
She is going to make her own tart.
她會自己做出果餡餅的
You,out.
你 出去啦
I am never gonna make this shell. I can't even get it in the pan right.
皮子真是做不出來了 都不能好好塞進盤子裡
Max,that looks right.
Max 我看挺好的
Oh,my God! I got it in the pan right! I can do this!
天哪! 塞進盤子裡了! 塞對了!
You did it! I knew it! I helped you. We're besties.
你做到了! 我就知道! 我幫到你了 我們真是好搭檔
You're not safe. Leave.
這裡不安全 你出去
I'm telling you,Max,I've tasted a lot of tarts,and yours is delicious.
跟你說 Max 我嘗過很多果餡餅 你的真不錯啊
You are not the first man to tell me that.
你不是第一個這麼說的男人了 (見前面tart雙關)
The first man to tell me that is in jail.
第一個這麼說的男人 現在坐牢呢
Here he comes. Look at him. Here he comes.
他來了 看啊 他來了
Afternoon,ladies.
下午好 女士們
Bien fondue,Eiffel Tower.
埃菲爾鐵塔 乾酪火鍋不錯呀
Okay.
好吧
Thank you for coming. Shall we begin the tasting?
謝謝你們過來 開始試吃吧?
This is exciting?
激動吧?
Keep it in your pants.
把持住
And now for the tart.
這個果餡餅呢
It's Max's first ever.
是Max做的第一個果餡餅
I ate a slice earlier and it was like Having a little piece of heaven.
我吃了一塊 味道似天堂
Don't do anything you're doing.
快給我剎車
It's flaky,creamy...
酥酥的 奶油味也很足
For a first attempt,I am very impressed.
對於初次嘗試 我覺得很不錯了
Don't be. I made a tart.
別啊 我只是做了個果餡餅
It's not like I cured herpes or invented a reverse microwave to instantly chill sodas.
又不是治好了皰疹 也沒有發明 反向運轉 能瞬間冰鎮飲料的微波爐
Okay,Max.
好了 Max
I will talk it over with my faculty and we will let you know.
我去給同事們嘗嘗 再告訴你決定
I'll let you know.
我會告訴你決定的
Nailed that.
拿下!
Max!
Max!
Stop stealing my things! You got a cleaning lady!
別偷我店裡東西了! 你不是有清潔工嗎?
Relax. I am returning what I took.
急什麼 我是把之前拿的還回來
Here's your plates.
你的盤子
Oh,and here's your ATM card. I lifted it from your wallet.
還有你的ATM卡 從你錢包裡順的
Oh,and here's your wallet.
對了 還有你錢包
There was $40 in here.
之前裡面有40塊
There sure was.
木有錯
At least give me back my gift card from Sephora.
至少把絲芙蘭的禮金卡 還給我吧?
Caroline,Han wants his Sephora gift card back.
Caroline Han叫你把絲芙蘭的禮金卡還給他
Oh,that's not happening. It's already on my face.
辦不到 已經用在我臉上了
- Max,look,it's from the pastry school. -  My acceptance letter!
- Max 你看 糕點學校寄來的 - 我的入學信嗎!
Lot of people talking about my chili in that bathroom.
廁所裡好多人都在談論 我做的辣椒醬啊
Oleg,come here. Han,Earl,stay.
Oleg 過來 Han Earl 也別走
You guys are about to owe me big.
你們就等著欠我大人情吧
I am gonna let you witness something extremely rare.
我要讓你們瞧瞧舉世罕見的東西
More rare than a sighting of Bigfoot or a UFO or Han's penis.
比大腳怪 UFO 以及Han的雞雞 都要罕見
You held me here so I could hear that?
你不讓我走 就是為了當面損我?
Behold,the rarest sight of them all.
看吧 世上最稀罕的東西!
You are about to see something good actually happen to me.
你們將要看到 好事終於降臨到我頭上了
Listen to this.
聽好了
"Dear Ms. Black,after careful consideration"of our large pool of applicants,we regret to inform you..."
"親愛的Black女士 經過對 眾多申請者的甄選 很遺憾地通知您"
Oh,I guess I didn't get in.
哦 估計我是沒被錄取
Looking back,we probably should have insisted she read that to herself,first.
回首往事 我們應該堅持 讓她自己先看的
I know why she didn't get in. Her name.
我知道為什麼不錄取她 她的名字
They saw the word "Black" and stopped reading.
一看到"Black"(黑) 就不往下看了
That's why I didn't get into law school.
我也是因為這個 沒念成法學院
I also didn't apply.
不過我也沒申請
This is terrible. I'm gonna go see if she's okay.
太慘了 我得去看看她好不好
Who does that French frog think he is?
那只法國青蛙以為他是誰啊!
He thinks he can have the time of his life tasting my tart and then never see me again?
吃了我的果餡餅 度過這輩子 最開心的時光 然後就不見我了?
He won't let me into his school?
不讓我念他的破學校是吧?
Well,I won't take no for an answer.
我還就不答應了
I am going down there right now and giving him a piece of my mind.
我現在就過去 告訴他我的想法!
I am storming out.
奪門而出啊我
And I am storming back in.
然後奪門而入
It is dark outside. That school's not open.
天都黑了 學校估計不開門
Hey,you. Tart tease,we need a word.
喂! 果餡餅噱頭師傅 給個話啊!
Oh,boy.
老天
What? You love my pastries
怎麼? 你不是覺得好吃嗎?
and then regret to inform me I'm not good enough for your school?
怎麼又遺憾地通知我不夠資格?
Well,I regret to inform you that I am good enough and I want to know why you won't let me in here.
那我也遺憾地通知你 我絕對夠格 麻煩你說說為什麼不錄取我
Okay,your voice is an anxiety trigger for me.
聽你這樣講話 我要焦慮了
I'm going to have to remove myself from the situation and go sit in the hallway.
我就不讓自己參與這種場合了 我去過道裡坐著吧
Can you come with me? You have a very calming presence.
你能跟我一起來嗎? 有你在覺得安心呢
Thank you. So few people think that about me.
謝謝 很少有人這麼說我的
But I should stay with Max.
不過我應該陪著Max
No,I got this handled. You can have her.
不用 我搞得定 你跟她去吧
This is the last time you give me to someone.
以後再不准你把我指派給別人
Max,your tart was excellent. The problem was your attitude.
Max 你的果餡餅無可挑剔 但你的態度有問題
You showed no passion of wanting to be in this school.
完全看不出你想加入本校的願望
And that is why you didn't get in. It seemed like you didn't want it.
這就是理由 你不是發自內心地想來這裡
No,no,no,that's just my attitude.
不不不 我的態度一貫這樣
I act like I don't want anything because I never got anything I wanted.
我就一副什麼也不在乎的樣子 因為在乎的東西永遠得不到
But I do want to go to this school more than I've ever wanted anything.
但我真的很想來這裡學習 比什麼都想
It's my fantasy and my dream,and please stop making me use these horrible,horrible words!
這是我的夢想追求啊 快不要再讓我 說這麼肉麻的詞了!
Just let me in,okay?
就錄取我唄
Okay.
好
Wait,for real?
等等 真的?
Yes. I needed to see if your passion was as good as your pastry and you just showed me it was.
真的 我就想看看 你的熱情是不是 和果餡餅口味一樣高 你表現出來了
I'm thrilled to have you on board,chef.
很高興有你加入 廚師
Thanks,chef.
多謝 廚師
Bebe is having a panic attack and needs to hold her lemon.
Bebe心臟病犯了 要拿她的檸檬
Has anyone seen her lemon?
有人見到她的檸檬了嗎?
Caroline,he let me in. I'm going to pastry school.
Caroline 他錄取我了 我要上糕點學校了!
Everybody has to call me "chef" now!
大家都要叫我"大師傅"了
You did it,chef!
你做到了 大師傅!
You're going to the pastry school from the brochure!
你要來念傳單上的糕點學校了!
Aren't you glad I looked at your porn?
是不是很慶幸 我看了你的黃書呀?
We're roommates. Both single. Quelle surprise.
我們是室友 都是單身 是不是很吃驚
So Max,once you fill out these,you will be officially enrolled.
Max 把這些填好 就正式入學了
And of course we will need your tuition check.
當然 學費支票也得交上來
Yup. $3,000. It's a lot for us.
行 三千嘛 對我們來說真不少
But if we make some cutbacks,1/2-ply toilet paper.
但要是我們省一省 一張廁紙分兩層用
Who am I kidding? No toilet paper,diner napkins.
我說啥呢! 不用廁紙了 就用餐巾吧
No,tuition is 24,000.
不 學費是兩萬四
But the brochure said $3,000 a year.
傳單上不是說三千一年嗎?
You misread it. It's $3,000 a unit.
你看錯了 是三千一個單元
There is eight units per year. 24,000.
每年八個單元 一共兩萬四
It costs $24,000? We can't pay that.
要兩萬四? 我們付不起啊
Oh,my God,now I'm never gonna be able to come here and I just admitted I wanted to!
天哪 這輩子都上不起這學校 我還剛承認自己特別想來!
I take back everything I ever said about wanting anything.
剛才說的想要什麼什麼 我全部收回
- Max,you can't just storm out. - Your face can't just storm out!
- Max 不要奪門而出啊 - 你才不要奪門而出!
Look,I will do anything for that girl to go to this school.
為了讓那姑娘上學 我什麼都願意做
In exchange for tuition,I could work in the office.
我可以來這辦公室上班 賺她的學費
Bebe clearly needs someone to help take the pressure off and who better than a mentally stable Wharton graduate like myself?
Bebe顯然需要有人幫她減壓
But I'll do anything. I'll even wash your floors,okay?
我什麼都肯幹 擦地板也行啊
Although I'm sure there's something better than that.
雖然肯定有比那更好的事情
But if you need me to wash the floors,I will wash the floors.
不過真要刷地板 我也願意
Really would prefer to do anything else,but I'll do it,'cause I'll do anything to get her into this school.
我當然更願意做別的 但只要能讓她上學 我什麼都肯
Please no floors.
拜託不要讓我擦地板
Okay,I will talk it over with my staff and I will let you know.
好吧 我跟員工商量一下 再通知你
Oh,no,no.
別別
I've seen what happens when you give people the "I'll let you know."
"再通知你"之後會發生什麼 我已經領教過了
I'm not going anywhere until you let me know to my face.
我不會走的 直到你當面通知我
With your face. Your beautiful,beautiful face.
直到你頂著那張帥到渣的臉 通知我
Max,we're not poor enough?
Max 還嫌我們不夠窮?
You're starting a hobo trash fire in our apartment?
開始在家裡點流浪漢垃圾火堆了?
Yup. I'm burning my porn and pastry school brochure.
是 黃書和糕點學校傳單都燒光
You know,all my fantasies.
所有的幻想都燒乾淨
If I learned anything in life it's that nothing's more flammable than my dreams.
要說生活給我的啟示 那就是 沒什麼比夢想更容易點著了
- Are those my slipper socks in there? - Yeah,those needed to die too.
- 那是我的地板襪嗎? - 對 它們也得死
Well,while you were in our living room hosting a burning man festival,
你在客廳燒得歡
I was at the pastry school getting us a work-study arrangement.
我在糕點學校 爭取到了學習/工作的安排
- You're going to pastry school. - No way!
- 你還是要去念糕點學校 - 不是吧!
Here you go. Your school uniform.
給 你的校服
This is where my name's gonna go!
我的名字就要寫在這裡哇!
My chef name,Conchita Bonfire.
我的廚師名 Conchita Bonfire (小淫娃·火堆)
Thank you for this.
謝謝你為我做這個
And for everything.
為我做的一切
You don't have to thank me.
不用謝我
'Cause with your new skills I'm gonna use you like Kim uses Kanye.
等你學了新技能 我就要像 Kim擺佈Kanye一樣 來擺佈你
Or Kanye uses Kim. I'm not sure which of them is winning.
或者是Kanye擺佈Kim 說不好誰贏呢
What kind of work-study arrangement did you make for me?
你給我爭取到了什麼 學習/工作的安排?
It's more of a work-study arrangement for us.
算是我們倆的學習/工作安排
I'll be working in the office helping out Bebe,so I'm working,you're studying.
我在辦公室協助Bebe 我工作 你學習
You're working at my school? Mom!
你在我學校上班? 媽!
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Sync: YTET-   定风波
-------------------------------------- 本論壇字幕僅翻譯交流學習之用 禁止任何商業用途否則後果自負 -------------------------------------- 破產姐妹 第三季 第09集 完
CURRENT TOTAL $
-=YTET-伊甸園字幕組=- 翻譯/校對: 歐屁屁 時間軸: 定風波
NEW TOTAL $
目前存款: 2.50